okay in fact let's make this our first shortcut
changing the scaling all right so a couple ways to do that first if you go
over to the top right and click the three dots you'll see that
you have some quick program scaling and that's a quick and
easy way to get in there and just grab and go
but it turns out there is a secret command and it's called set programming scaling to and then
you put in your percent 121 percent and that will allow you to quickly set it exactly what you want
and once you get it I recommend you do the following open favorites so go to tools type in
fav for favorites click on favorites and then what you do is you click on it type in your information
you'll see the drop down menu.
And once you get your sweet spot, left click on that and either
drag it to favorites over here at the left, or if it's something you frequently use, then just drag
it to the shortcut toolbar and release.
And then you can right click on that, give it a name.
You might want to just, I like leaving the whole command in there.
That way I can reaccess the
command.
But now you've got it.
You can just click it and boom, you've got that setting available for
you at any time and that's nice when you're changing screens or moving Logos to different
resolutions or use on different computers.